(Leonard:)I came here to apologize.
(Penny:)Okay. Leonard,
I really appreciate that,
(Penny:)but I need a little time
to myself.
Wha... Okay. I don't get it.
(Leonard:)You said make an effort.
(Leonard:)Here I am, making an effort.
(Sheldon:)Hello, Amy. It's
nice to see you.
(Amy:)Nice to see you, too.
(Sheldon:)And that's how you make
effort look effortless.
(Howard:)All right.
Can you please just go
(Penny:)and we'll talk
about this tomorrow?
(Leonard:)I don't understand
what you want!
I'm trying to figure it out!
(Sheldon:)You know what? If you'd like,
(Sheldon:)I could whip up a quick
Relationship Agreement.
(Sheldon:)Well, I'm at a spa,
(Sheldon:)might as well do
something relaxing.
(Amy:)Sheldon, why don't
we give them some privacy?
(Sheldon:)Very well.
(Sheldon:)Hey. Later, we'll check
out the minibar?
(Sheldon:)I'll show you
how Godzilla gets drunk.
(Howard:)So what we did was map
out the entire room
(Howard:)to identify every squeak.
(Howard:)Watch. It's easy,
once you get the hang of it.
(Raj:)Step.